{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 0,
      "question": "Why do you want to be part of YC?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "For mentorship and education. We don’t know what we don’t know and feel the guidance Y Combinator would provide would enable us to concentrate on building the product and the company while avoiding costly mistake"
    },
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Why is your product priced the way it is?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "We look at our margin goals and what we think the market will bear based on competitor pricing"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "If your startup succeeds, what additional areas could you expand into?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "All women's apparel that requires breast support and shapewear"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "What's the biggest mistake you have made?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "Thinking that other people were motivated by the same things I was and thought like I do.  To be persuasive, you must work to understand how other people are motivated and adapt your message accordingly."
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "What will be your biggest challenge two years from now?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "Competition from fast fashion"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Who are your competitors?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "OGL Move, Popilush, lululemon, Uniqlo"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "What makes your product different from existing options?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "Every single competitor in this space is using an antiquated solution from the 1980s that is heavy and hot. Although it is easier than wearing a bra + garment, it doesn’t FEEL better than wearing a bra + garment.  Our innovation is a lining that feels like a second skin. It feels better than going braless, it feels better than wearing a bra"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Who would you hire, or how would you add to your team?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "Marketing is at the top of our list"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "How are you working to expand geographically?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "We will begin by starting our North America business in the USA. We have a licensing agreement in works for Victoria’s Secret China"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "What do you understand about your customers?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "As one of the world’s leading bra experts, I’ve personally fit bras on at least 1500 women. In those intimate settings, I’ve heard women’s complaints about bras, what they wish they could find in the market, and their frustrations of trying to find the right bra for the right garment. Their complaints echoed my own frustrations with bra wearing and shopping. As both the target customer, and a leading domain expert, I understand what is missing in the market and I know clothing with an integrated bra-like solution is wanted and needed"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "How will you make money?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "Why isn't someone already doing this?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": " Some other brands are already doing this, but they are using an antiquated solution that’s inexpensive to produce but doesn’t make the experience of wearing the garment any better than wearing a bra"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "What do you know about this space/product others don't know?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "Most founders who start companies in this space are not domain experts. They’re well-meaning people who must rely on the factory to create the garments. Factories don’t work against their own best interest which means they want to make things the way they’ve always made them. Because of our close factory partnerships, and because I personally know how to operate all the machines in the factory as well as I make my own patterns, we can work with the manufacturers to create truly innovative solutions using new manufacturing methods"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "What is the next step with the product evolution?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "To expand into garments that can be worn at work and out to a date. And also to create clothes that smooth without shapewear, thereby eliminating the need for granny panties"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "How do you know customers need what you're making?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "As one of the world’s leading bra experts, I’ve personally fit bras on at least 1500 women. No focus group or questionnaire could ever replicate the type of data gathered in those intimate bra fitting settings. I’ve heard women’s complaints about bras, what they wish they could find in the market, and their frustrations of trying to find the right bra for the right garment. Their complaints echoed my own frustrations with bra wearing and shopping"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "Who would be your next hire?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "Someone who is excited to share our product with the world (marketing) and is willing to think outside the box"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "How long can you go before funding?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "Our runway is about 3 months"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "Someone just showed us an idea like this right before you guys. I don't like it. What else do you have?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "We could concentrate solely on manufacturing innovative bras, sports bras, and panties"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "Will you incorporate as a US company?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "We are already incorporated in Delaware as a C corp"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "How will you get users?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "Roadshows and pop-ups to begin with, influencers, and social media ads"
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "Will your team stick at this?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "20 TBD"
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "question": "Have you raised funding?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "We have raised a modest friends and family round and issued SAFE notes"
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "question": "What is your burn rate?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "***Burn rate is he rate at which a company consumes its cash, usually measured monthly**"
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "question": "How do you know people want this?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "As one of the world’s leading bra experts, I’ve personally fit bras on at least 1500 women. In those intimate settings, I’ve heard women’s complaints about bras, what they wish they could find in the market, and their frustrations of trying to find the right bra for the right garment. Their complaints echoed my own frustrations with bra wearing and shopping. The garments I’m creating are things I’m seeking myself in the market but cannot find. I have the advantage of being both the target customer and a leading domain expert.  Interviews with other target customers have validated the need for this type of beast support built-in clothing solution as well as the number of competitors starting to fill this space"
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "question": "What's the funniest thing that has happened to you?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "I built and played a homemade instrument at the Miss Northern California pageant which is part of the Miss America pageant circuit. It was a bit “Little Miss Sunshine” and a bit “Miss Congeniality"
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "question": "Where will you locate?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "We are still evaluating in which city/state to locate the headquarters. The parameters we are considering are: proximity to talent, proximity to international airport, taxes, quality of life, and cost of living"
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "question": "Tell us something surprising you have done?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "I built and played a homemade instrument at the Miss Northern California pageant which is part of the Miss America pageant circuit"
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "question": "How are you meeting customers?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "Roadshows and pop-ups"
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "question": "What obstacles will you face and how will you overcome them?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "Competition from fast fashion. The only way to stay ahead of this is to constantly innovate. It’s pointless and costly to try to litigate the copycats. I have dozens of ideas I haven’t executed yet and I believe the combination of a strong brand with a strong why + true innovation will keep customers loyal to us"
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "question": "What else have you created together?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "TAD"
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "question": "How will customers and/or users find out about you?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "Social media, in person pop-ups and roadshows, and word of mouth"
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "question": "What's new about what you make?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "For the built-in bras we have innovated the fabrics to create ultra-lightweight support that feels like a second skin. This is new in the market. Our invisilace which doesn’t show under clothes is also new in the market. Our self-fastening bra closure will be the first of its kind in the world. Our bra has a lining which is the first of its kind in the market. I have dozens of other ideas I haven’t executed yet"
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "question": "Who would use your product?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "Anyone who has breasts. We believe the T shirt will be popular with younger consumers, 18-25 years old, and they will evangelize it with their mothers which will introduce our product to a larger age range"
    },
    {
      "id": 33,
      "question": "Who needs what you're making?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": " Anyone who has breasts. We believe the T shirt will be popular with younger consumers, 18-25 years old, and they will evangelize it with their mothers which will introduce our product to a larger age range"
    },
    {
      "id": 34,
      "question": "What products are you going to build first?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "We are going to start with the products that most resonated with consumers in the wear test"
    },
    {
      "id": 35,
      "question": "Why will you succeed?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "35 We will succeed because customers want better breast support, we have a good team, and we are willing to listen and learn"
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "question": "What is your user growth rate?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "We don't know yet.  We hope our products will have strong word-of-mouth, with each customer strongly recommending to several of her friends.  That is, our intention is to generate viral growth via exceptional customer satisfaction"
    },
    {
      "id": 37,
      "question": "Who is the boss?",
      "owner": "Ben",
      "answer": "For important decisions, the buck stops with Laura.  I provide input and own all the decisions about production, supply chain, materials, and for anything else Laura makes the executive decision"
    },
    {
      "id": 38,
      "question": "What systems have you hacked?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "38 TBD"
    },
    {
      "id": 39,
      "question": "What domain expertise do you have?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "I am the only person in North America with a masters degree in lingerie design and I am considered one of the world’s foremost bra experts. I’m also an innovator with eight patents who is constantly thinking about how we can make things better"
    },
    {
      "id": 40,
      "question": "What are the key things about your field that outsiders don't understand?",
      "owner": "Laura",
      "answer": "Most people don’t understand how bra production has been the same for nearly fifty years and the factories who make bras are not interested in change. Also bra production is closer to footwear production than it is to apparel production. People who don’t understand this industry who try to launch startups in it are beholden to the factories antiquated manufacturing methods. It’s true that you need to know the rules to know how to break the rules and, in this case, knowing the rules, and knowing how to operate the factory machinery, are both needed to truly innovate these products"
    },
    { "id": 41,
      "question": "What is your supply chain strategy?",
      "owner": "Ben",
      "answer": "Will start with demand-driven.  As we plan Shopify as a selling channel, we can get the real time sales status. Through MRP system, the whole supply chain also get the related order details shortly, check inventory status and react to the demand accordingly."
    },
    { "id": 42,
      "question":"What is your backup plan if your supply chain has disruptions?",
      "owner":"Ben",
      "answer": "With my extensive sourcing relationships in the sourcing business for major brands, we could pivot to new suppliers for both raw material and garment manufacturing if disruptions occur. Each of our manufacturing partners already identified that could reallocate products to other countries if necessary"
    },
    {"id": 43, 
      "question": "How will you manage 3PL?", 
      "owner":"Ben", 
      "answer":"We are still investigating the right 3PL partner but have a few identified. Weare also investigating managing 3PL from Asia direct to consumerIn the short term, considering pick & pack and delivery set up at the finished goods region/country. Work with a 3PL partner who has warehouse to collect & distribute in multi-locations and with a sophisticate cloud-based system can bridge with Shopify so that we can get the real time sells and inventory status. For long term, boat shipment to US warehouse of the 3PL partner, pick and pack and arrange local delivery"
},
        {
      "id": 44,
      "question": "Ho will you deal with China Tariffs?",
      "owner": "Ben",
"answer": "3PL can be the short-term solution. On the other hand, each of our factories and mills own production entities in other countries including Vietnam, Thailand, Indonesia, Sri Lanka and India...etc. We can move production if we need to, and we’ve already started those conversations. Because we haven’t launched yet, we can adjust our pricing and sourcing strategy accordingly once the tariffs are set from the US Government. We’re waiting to see what the US Government decides before we adjust our strategy. Whatever happens, all companies producing in China will need to figure this out."
    },
    {"id":45,
      "question":"Tell us more about your plans to make apparel manufacturing more agile by putting product development in Asia",
      "owner":"Laura",
      "answer":"All major brands based in the USA are using a decades old model of having their pattern makers and technical designers based in the USA. This model requires the prototyping process to take months instead of days due to the back and forth between Asia and the USA and the need to wait for the prototypes to be shipped back and forth. The most talented patternmakers and technical designers are based at the factories, in our case, in Asia. Keeping product development close to the factories means we can turn around prototypes in days not months."
    },

    {"id":46,
      "question":"Why do you have so little equity",
      "owner":"Ben",
      "answer":"47 TBD"
    },
    {"id":47,
      "question":"Where did your $25MM number come from",
      "owner":"Ben",
      "answer":"48 TBD"
    }
      
    
  ]
}
